<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Quinnb</title>
    <link>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Quinnb</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 15:12:47 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Soundwave Wallpaper</title>
      <link>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/soundwave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 15:12:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/soundwave/</guid>
      <description>So this is a wallpaper I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on, not sure why anyone would want to use it, but here it is!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Linux Community</title>
      <link>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/linux-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 19:12:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/linux-community/</guid>
      <description>The linux community is a gong show in my opinion. On one hand, you&amp;rsquo;ve got these asshole free software evangelists who happen to be politically far right assholes, and on the other, you&amp;rsquo;ve got people who&amp;rsquo;s entire vocabulary is comprised of the words I, Use, Arch, by, the, and way. It really is a shame in some respects, because there are some decent linux communities. I generally find people who use ubuntu don&amp;rsquo;t care as much about free software, and have much more centered political views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Good Knife</title>
      <link>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/a-good-knife/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 15:21:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/a-good-knife/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s no denying the usefulness of a good pocket knife. They make useful fidget toys for when you&amp;rsquo;re bored, they can open boxes, and a ton of other things. An entry level knife can be picked up for around $40, which considering the convenience you&amp;rsquo;re getting, is a really good price. I think that everyone should get a knife, due to how useful they are. Some even have can openers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sony Discman D-E201</title>
      <link>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/de201/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 14:40:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/de201/</guid>
      <description>This is the Discman D-E201 A while ago I was listening to what at the time was the latest episode the patreon only This Does Not Compute Podcast. The episode was on how CDs were making a return, and how now if you thought a discman might be something you want, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to pick one up. I went on ebay just for fun to see what I could find, and ended up picking up a Discman D-E201 with ESP2 protection (stops the disc from skipping using a buffer).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 14:22:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quinnb.xyz/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Hi There! I&amp;rsquo;m Quinn, welcome to my blog. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried this before, and never really stuck with it, mainly because I was pushing just an exported version of my hugo site to github, not the full source. Anyways, I&amp;rsquo;m planning to write some cool stuff on here, so definitely be on the lookout!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
